---
description: Base app instructions
globs: 
alwaysApply: false
---

# Your rule content
This app is called "supapost", which is an ai post generator for X (formerly Twitter) service. It consists of this app, and it will also have a browser extension to make it easier for suers to generate/reply to posts directly on X. This app is using Wave, a laravel framework by dojo.

Documentation for Wave framework can be found here: https://devdojo.com/wave/docs/getting-started

---
description: Database rules for Supapost project
globs: ["**/*.php", "**/*.js", "**/*.ts"]
alwaysApply: true
---

# Supapost Database Rules

When working with database operations in this project, always refer to the database schema defined in `supapost.sql`.

## Database Overview
This app is called "supapost", which is an AI post generator for X (formerly Twitter) service. It consists of this app, and it will also have a browser extension to make it easier for users to generate/reply to posts directly on X. This app is using Wave, a Laravel framework by dojo.

## Database Tables
The database includes the following key tables:
- `users` - User accounts and authentication
- `posts` - Generated posts and content
- `categories` - Content categorization
- `api_keys` - API authentication keys
- `changelogs` - System update logs
- `early_subscriptions` - Early access subscribers
- `forms` - Dynamic form definitions
- `form_entries` - Form submission data
- `migrations` - Database migration history
- `model_has_permissions` - Permission assignments
- `model_has_roles` - Role assignments
- `notifications` - User notifications
- `pages` - Static page content
- `plans` - Subscription plans
- `subscriptions` - User subscriptions

## Database Validation Rules
- Always use `exists:table_name,column_name` for foreign key validations
- Use `unique:table_name,column_name` for unique field validations
- For nullable foreign keys, use `nullable|exists:table_name,column_name`

## Query Guidelines
- Use prepared statements for all database queries
- Avoid raw queries when possible
- Use Eloquent relationships for related data
- Implement proper indexing for frequently queried columns

## Security Considerations
- Never expose database credentials in code
- Sanitize all user inputs before database operations
- Implement proper access control for database operations
- Use migrations for all database schema changes

## Post Credits System
- Users have post credits associated with their accounts
- Plans define the number of post credits available
- Track and validate post credit usage before generating new content

- You can @ files here
- You can use markdown but dont have to
